Contact

House # 9 Block 80 sector 5D north karachi, Karachi 0341-2682080 (Mobile) hamzakhann66@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/m-hamza-khan-a10470128 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript

React.js

Angular

Languages

English (Limited Working)
Urdu (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Building Offline Web Apps with Service Workers

Multiplatform Mobile App Development with React Native

Server-side Development with NodeJS, Express and MongoDB

AWS Fundamentals: Building Serverless Applications

Full-Stack Web Development with React Specialization

M HAMZA KHAN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Summary

Hi, I am Hamza Khan from Pakistan, I am a passionate Full stack developer with more than 4 years experience working for many companies and startups, I love to create applications around web and mobile with neat and clean code using best practices, test driven approach, latest trends in technology and using scalable architecture. Launched multiple projects with different teams. I am always ready for new challanges.

Current Interest in Web 3.0 technologies and trying to learn Blockchain, NFTs, Smart Contracts.

Experience

Mintdropz
Full Stack Engineer
August 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months)
United States

Working on NFT Projects

Ruvivo.ai
Full Stack Engineer
January 2020 - August 2021 (1 year 8 months)
United States

Working on AI based platform for call centers!.

Soprano.tv Front End Architect August 2020 - December 2020 (5 months) United States

Working on OTT platform Dame Dash Studios

RightBound Full Stack Engineer December 2019 - August 2020 (9 months) **United States**

Working on Reporting Module implementing Charts

HolonIQ

Frontend Developer August 2019 - December 2019 (5 months)

United States

Working on tables charts data modelling and APIs integration

Panacloud Pvt Ltd

Internee

December 2018 - November 2019 (1 year)

Karachi

Selected as a bootcamper after passing some axams and start learning latest technologies like Docker Kubernetes AWS Ansible CI CD

Education

ILMA University - Formerly IBT BSCS, Computer Science · (2016 - 2020)

The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology Specializaion, Computer Software Engineering (2018 - 2019)

Aligarh institute of technology pakistan

High School Diploma, Electrical and Electronics Engineering (2011 - 2014)